LE THI MY LINH

.NET DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Phone: (+84) 356 444 804

Email/Skype: linhltm.uit@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://e-mi-ly.github.io/portfolio/

PROFILE

I am a nearly 5 years of experience in software development, specializing in .NET Developer and have 2 years in React and front-end web technologies.

My job is to build scalable and efficient web applications. Strong problem-solving abilities and a passion for continuous learning and improvement. Currently seeking opportunities to grow as a full-stack engineer and a senior web developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mediastep Software Inc. | 02/2023 - Present Intermediate .NET Developer

Responsibilities:

- Participate in the implementation of new features for upcoming versions as a full-stack web developer.
- Fix bugs and improve performance related to the current system flow as well as existing functionalities.
- Actively collaborate with other departments, such as Business Analysts, to receive, clarify, and address requirements for implementation. Work with Quality Assurance to ensure that functions meet all customer use cases.
- Demonstrate strong teamwork abilities, including discussing, dividing tasks, and addressing issues related to the technologies used and challenges encountered during implementation.
- Write and optimize SQL stored procedures, views, and functions

Project: Auvenir is an intelligent, cloud-based client engagement platform that enables firms to leverage the best of today's technology to create a better engagement experience for practitioners and their respective clients. Auvenir helps build a better engagement experience for firms and organizations, their teams, and their clients.

Technologies:

- .NET Core, HTML, CSS, React, EF Core, LINQ, SSO, SignalR, Redis, SharePoint, Spreadjs, DevExpress
- Database: SQL Server
- Design pattern: DI, Repository, UoW, Factory, Microservices
- Microsoft Azure, Azure DevOps, Azure Functions, Service Bus, Blob Storage

GVI HCM - Global Vertical Innovations, LLC | 07/2020 - 01/2023

Back-end Developer

Responsibility: Join the team to develop the web for the E-Commerce system. Analysis requirements, research, meeting to design the infrastructure of the project, break tasks, estimate, and implement the functions essential and integration.

Project: Payment System

- The payment system is designed to enable users from third-party applications to pay
 their invoices via supported payment service providers or endpoints. This would be the
 primary method of revenue collection within RIVIR and be interlinked directly into the
 downstream accounting and reporting.
- Technologies: .NET Core, EF Core, Identity Server4, Authorize.net, FTP, SQL Server

Project: RIVIR

- RIVIR is a web-based application where Sellers, Brokers, Manufacturing, and Retailer register their products which are certified as GS1 standards to improve efficiency, safety, and visibility, and shared key information about products with end-users.
- · Technologies:
 - .NET Core, EF Core, Hangfire, Serilog, RestSharp, Identity Server4, SignalR
 - Database: SQL Server, MongoDB
 - Search engine: Elasticsearch
 - File: Aspose.Cells, Aspose.Words, Aspose.Slides, Aspose.PDF, Dropbox, Google Cloud Storage, Image Magick
 - Google Cloud Platform
 - Source management: Azure DevOps

EDUCATION

University of Information Technology - UIT | 2015-2020

Software Engineering

GPA: 8.11/10

English

I am able to use English to communicate effectively, exchange and receive information from customers, read and understand requirements and business documents to compile them into technical documents.

• TOEIC: 775/990 - IIG Vietnam

STRENGTHS

Familiar with Agile - SCRUM

Experience in version control: GIT

Problem solving

Quick learner

Multitasking

Time management

Good communication - teamwork

Work well under pressure